Charlie Elliott

The Ultimate Dinning Experience Guru

Oakland, CA 94603 elliottcharlie211@gmail.com 5107766631

Diligent Dependable Reliable Hospitality Specialist, seeking a full -time position in the restaurant field. I have obtain over twenty years of extensive food service skills plus customer service and cash handling skills are at broader levels. Very detailed orientated and multitasking experience makes me a great candidate for a fast pace full dinning restaurant.

Willing to relocate to: Concord, CA - Hayward, CA - San Francisco, CA

Work Experience

Sanitation Worker

Saag's - San Leandro, CA July 2018 to Present

My job is to clean and sanitize all equipment that is use by the product manufacturering department in the to be cook to the read to be eating areas .

Food Server

Denny Restaurant - San Pablo, CA October 2008 to March 2018

Food Server / Shift Lead

T.G.I Fridays - San Bruno, CA December 2000 to January 2008

Food Server Director

T.G.I Fridays - Oakland, CA January 1996 to November 2000

Education

Associate

Laney College

Diploma

Berkeley High School

Skills

Multitasking Skills, Detail Oriented, Cash Handling, Cash Register, Customer Service Skills, Bartending Skills, Prep Cook, Server Skills, Assembly, Clean, Food Production, Janitorial

Certifications/Licenses

Food Handler

November 2017 to November 2020

Food Handler (Basic Certification)

Driver's License

Additional Information

I am a very hard working single parent that's reliable and dependable & knowledgeable in the restaurant field. looking for a restaurant to show case my skills and build clientele and revenue for the restaurant and my self , im available for dinner shifts Weekends and Holidays.